https://www.wildhorseresort.com/privacy-policy/

Close
Need Help?Wildhorse Resort & Casino is committed to promoting responsible gambling. Oregon Problem Gambling Resources is for individuals and family members who need help or have been impacted by a gambling problem. Treatment is free and confidential. If you or someone you know, has a gambling problem, visit www.OPGR.org or call 1-877-MY-LIMIT (69-54648) or text 503-713-6000Online Privacy PolicyWe appreciate your visit to our website.  Wildhorse Resort & Casino maintains this website to provide information to the public about our gaming, dining, golf, hotel and entertainment services and amenities.  Wildhorse Resort & Casino respects the privacy of all visitors to this site.  In order to provide the best service to our customers, we may collect certain non-identifying information from visitors to this site.  We may also require certain personal and/or financial information if you are making reservations or purchases or requesting information from us over the Internet. This Privacy Policy details what information we may collect and how it may be used.  All efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy of the information provided on this website; however, we make no warranties or representations as to the accuracy of this information.Automatically Collected Non-Identifying InformationWe may collect and use certain information about your use of this website that does not personally identify you, including your IP address and other information gathered by “cookies.”   This information may include pages viewed, date and time of visits to the website, type of browser and/or computer used and the domain name of the website, if any, from which you linked to our website.  This information does not personally identify you.  We collect it to help us develop generic profiles of users so that we can better serve our customers.  If you do not want your information to be collected by cookies, you should be able to set your web browser to reject cookies.  If you choose to reject cookies you may not be able to take advantage of certain options on this website.Personal InformationTo make reservations or purchases via this website, to receive information from us or to participate in contests or promotions, you may be required to provide personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, and/or email address.  By providing such information, you agree to be placed on marketing lists and to receive promotional materials from Wildhorse Resort & Casino.  You can update any personal information you provide to us if you wish.We store personal information provided by customers on secure servers. This website allows the transmission of personal information via secured and encrypted channels, provided that you use a similarly equipped web browser. Access to personally identifiable information which has been provided to us is strictly limited to Wildhorse Resort & Casino employees on a “need to know” basis.  While we strive to protect your personal information, Wildhorse cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us.  Therefore, should you choose to provide personal information, you do so at your own risk.Age PolicyGaming at Wildhorse Resort and Casino is restricted to persons aged 21 and above (ages 18 and above for bingo and Poker).  We have no intention to collect any personal information from anyone under gaming age. Offers, promotions, or contests we conduct are not open to persons under 21 (ages 18 and above for Bingo and Poker).  We reserve the right to verify age at any time for any reason and may reject anyone who does not produce legal, valid identification upon request.  If a minor has provided us with personal information such as name, address, telephone number or email address, their parent or guardian should contact us as provided below to identify all information to be removed.Sharing InformationWe will not share your personal information with any non-affiliated third parties, except when such disclosure may be necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process or legal requirement of any governmental authority, including but not limited to authorities that regulate gaming activities; or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Wildhorse Resort & Casino or the Confederated Tribes of the Umatilla Indian Reservation.This website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. We have no control over the use of other sites.  You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.Changes to Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy simply by posting such change, update, or modification on this website. Any change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting.OwnershipWildhorse Resort & Casino is owned and operated by the Confederated Tribes of the Umatilla Indian Reservation.  Nothing on this website is intended to nor shall in any way limit or subject the sovereignty of Wildhorse Resort & Casino or the Umatilla Tribal Government.CopyrightAll contents of this Website are: Copyright © 2010 Wildhorse Resort and Casino, 46510 Wildhorse Blvd, Pendleton, OR, 97801. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Join Our Mailing List
Contact Us
COVID-19 Update
Team Wild Update
Tamástslikt Cultural Institute
Wildhorse Foundation
Wildhorse Donations
CTUIR
